question_data = [
    {
        "category": "Science: Astronomy",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The Earth is the third planet from the Sun.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science: Astronomy",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The Moon orbits the Earth.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science: Astronomy",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The Sun is a star.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science: Astronomy",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Pluto is considered a planet.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science: Astronomy",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Saturn is the only planet in the solar system with rings.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science: Astronomy",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "The Andromeda Galaxy is the closest galaxy to the Milky Way.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science: Astronomy",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "A light year measures distance, not time.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science: Astronomy",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": " The Hubble Space Telescope is named after a famous astronomer.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science: Astronomy",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": " The phenomenon known as the 'redshift' indicates that galaxies are moving away from us.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science: Astronomy",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "The International Space Station (ISS) is located in geostationary orbit.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    }
]
